ALICE MCKAY

PROFILE

My retail career is comprised of three years of comprehensive sales floor and stockroom experience. I have vast experience with multiple till systems with a strong skillset in customer service, with the ability to provide a support to a diverse range of customers within the community, in a fast-paced public based environment.

CONTACT DETAILS

PHONE NUMBER 07563110867

EMAIL ADDRESS alimacy2508@gmail.com

EDUCATION

JUNIOR DEVELOPER DIPLOMA 2023-Present SheCodes

BA (HONS) HISTORY AND PHILOSOPHY 2:1
2018-2021 Queens University Belfast

A LEVELS: ENGLISH LITERATURE (B),
FRENCH (B), HISTORY(B)
2016-2018 Glenlola Collegiate School

9 GCSES AT GRADES(A*-B) INCLUDING
ENGLISH LITERATURE AND
MATHEMATICS
2014-2016 Glenlola Collegiate School

EXPERIENCE

SALES ASSISTANT, RIVER ISLAND - 2024-PRESENT

My role within River Island focuses primarily on providing exceptional customer service in an efficient and timely manner. I consistently supervise the men's and women's sales floors independently, taking responsibility for providing support for my customers as well as maintaining the visual standard of the store.

SELF SERVICE ATTENDANT - TESCO - 2023-2024

My work as a self service attendant was customer centric and heavily featured the use of strong communication and teamwork. I consistently worked to build strong client relationships and to troubleshoot problems in order to provide a diverse range of customers with a smooth and pleasant transaction.

STOCKROOM ASSISTANT - NEXT RETAIL LTD 2021-2023

My position within Next revolved around leading the womenswear section of the delivery team, managing the transferral of online returns, and training new members of staff in stockroom procedures. I ensured that my team members felt supported and worked together to reach our goal in a cohesive and timely manner.

INTERESTS

I am currently working through a front end development coding diploma with SheCodes, with modules featuring work on backend programming and data analysis., providing me with knowledge of HTML, CSS, Javascript as well as Python. Despite my academic career revolving primarily around art subjects, I have a deep interest in developing my programming knowledge and I have the ability to understand and learn new skills quickly.

I enjoy being creative and have a strong enthusiasm for developing my artistic skills and using them to engage with my local and national communities. I have opened my own small store on Redbubble and hope to continue to build on it. I was chosen as the winner of a British craft business's, Heidifeathers, needle felting competition. The photograph of my creation was displayed on their business cards and on their Facebook page.